Oliver Otis Howard Papers M091 M091
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- M91.5: Correspondence, eastern command period, December 1888-November 1894, M91.5; 9.25 linear feet
  - 1894 Mar 09 - 1894 Mar 11 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 1894 Mar 12 - 1894 Mar 13 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 1894 Mar 14 - 1894 Mar 15 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 1894 Mar 16 - 1894 Mar 17 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - 1894 Mar 19 - 1894 Mar 22 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 1894 Mar 23 - 1894 Mar 26 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 1894 Mar 27 - 1894 Mar 29 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 1894 Mar 30 - 1894 Mar 31 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - 1894 Apr 01 - 1894 Apr 02 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - 1894 Apr 03 - 1894 Apr 05 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - 1894 Apr 06 - 1894 Apr 07 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - 1894 Apr 08 - 1894 Apr 10 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - 1894 Apr 11 - 1894 Apr 12 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - 1894 Apr 13 - 1894 Apr 14 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - 1894 Apr 16 - 1894 Apr 17 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - 1894 Apr 18 - 1894 Apr 19 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - 1894 Apr 20 - 1894 Apr 21 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - 1894 Apr 22 - 1894 Apr 23 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - 1894 Apr 24 - 1894 Apr 26 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - 1894 Apr 27 - 1894 Apr 28 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - 1894 Apr 29 - 1894 Apr 30 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - 1894 May 01 - 1894 May 02 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - 1894 May 03 - 1894 May 04 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - 1894 May 05 - 1894 May 06 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - 1894 May 07 - 1894 May 08 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - 1894 May 09 - 1894 May 10 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - 1894 May 11 - 1894 May 13 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - 1894 May 14 - 1894 May 16 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - 1894 May 17 - 1894 May 18 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - 1894 May 19 - 1894 May 21 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - 1894 May 22 - 1894 May 25 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - 1894 May 26 - 1894 May 28 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - 1894 May 29 - 1894 May 31 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - 1894 Jun 01 - 1894 Jun 03 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - 1894 Jun 04 - 1894 Jun 05 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - 1894 Jun 06 - 1894 Jun 11 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - 1894 Jun 12 - 1894 Jun 15 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - 1894 Jun 16 - 1894 Jun 17 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - 1894 Jun 18 - 1894 Jun 19 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - 1894 Jun 20 - 1894 Jun 21 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - 1894 Jun 22 - 1894 Jun 23 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - 1894 Jun 24 - 1894 Jun 26 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - 1894 Jun 27 - 1894 Jun 30 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - 1894 Jul 01 - 1894 Jul 07 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - 1894 Jul 09 - 1894 Jul 12 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - 1894 Jul 13 - 1894 Jul 14 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - 1894 Jul 15 - 1894 Jul 17 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - 1894 Jul 18 - 1894 Jul 20 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - 1894 Jul 21 - 1894 Jul 24 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - 1894 Jul 25 - 1894 Jul 26 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - 1894 Jul 27 - 1894 Jul 31 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - 1894 Aug 01 - 1894 Aug 05 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - 1894 Aug 06 - 1894 Aug 07 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - 1894 Aug 08 - 1894 Aug 11 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - 1894 Aug 12 - 1894 Aug 14 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - 1894 Aug 15 - 1894 Aug 17 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - 1894 Aug 18 - 1894 Aug 21 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - 1894 Aug 22 - 1894 Aug 23 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - 1894 Aug 24 - 1894 Aug 27 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - 1894 Aug 28 - 1894 Aug 31 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - 1894 Sep 01 - 1894 Sep 03 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - 1894 Sep 04 - 1894 Sep 06 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - 1894 Sep 07 - 1894 Sep 10 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - 1894 Sep 11 - 1894 Sep 13 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - 1894 Sep 14 - 1894 Sep 15 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - 1894 Sep 16 - 1894 Sep 18 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - 1894 Sep 19 - 1894 Sep 20 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - 1894 Sep 21 - 1894 Sep 24 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - 1894 Sep 25 - 1894 Sep 27 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - 1894 Sep 28 - 1894 Sep 30 (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - 1894 Oct 01 - 1894 Oct 04 (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - 1894 Oct 05 - 1894 Oct 09 (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - 1894 Oct 10 - 1894 Oct 13 (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - 1894 Oct 14 - 1894 Oct 16 (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - 1894 Oct 17 - 1894 Oct 19 (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - 1894 Oct 20 - 1894 Oct 24 (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - 1894 Oct 25 - 1894 Oct 28 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - 1894 Oct 29 - 1894 Oct 31 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 1894 Nov 01 - 1894 Nov 04 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 1894 Nov 05 - 1894 Nov 06 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 1894 Nov 07 - 1894 Nov 08 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 1894 Nov 09 - 1894 Nov 10 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 1894 Nov 11 - 1894 Nov 12 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - 1894 Nov 13 - 1894 Nov 15 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - 1894 Nov 16 - 1894 Nov 19 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 1894 Nov 20 - 1894 Nov 24 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - 1894 Nov 25 - 1894 Nov 30 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- M91.6: Correspondence, retirement, December 1894-1912, undated, M91.6; 8.5 linear feet
  Correspondence, mostly letters received by Howard (letters sent are contained in letterpress volumes, M91.7) dealing with Howard's life after retiring from the army, 1894 to 1908. Incomplete indexes (M91.9) are available for use in Special Collections, Much of the material involves his work with education, especially with the founding of the Harrow School and Lincoln Memorial University, and his service on the boards of Bowdoin College and Norwich University. Howard also continued active with military and church organizations and societies.
  - 1894 Dec 01 - 1894 Dec 04 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 1894 Dec 05 - 1894 Dec 07 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - 1894 Dec 08 - 1894 Dec 10 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - 1894 Dec 11 - 1894 Dec 14 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - 1894 Dec 15 - 1894 Dec 18 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - 1894 Dec 19 - 1894 Dec 22 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - 1894 Dec 24 - 1894 Dec 27 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - 1894 Dec 28 - 1894 Dec 31 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - 1895 Jan 01 - 1895 Jan 04 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - 1895 Jan 05 - 1895 Jan 09 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - 1895 Jan 10 - 1895 Jan 12 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - 1895 Jan 13 - 1895 Jan 14 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - 1895 Jan 15 - 1895 Jan 17 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - 1895 Jan 18 - 1895 Jan 21 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - 1895 Jan 22 - 1895 Jan 23 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - 1895 Jan 24 - 1895 Jan 25 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - 1895 Jan 26 - 1895 Jan 28 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - 1895 Jan 29 - 1895 Jan 31 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - 1895 Feb 01 - 1895 Feb 05 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - 1895 Feb 06 - 1895 Feb 08 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - 1895 Feb 09 - 1895 Feb 12 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - 1895 Feb 13 - 1895 Feb 15 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - 1895 Feb 16 - 1895 Feb 19 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - 1895 Feb 20 - 1895 Feb 21 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - 1895 Feb 22 - 1895 Feb 25 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - 1895 Feb 26 - 1895 Feb 28 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - 1895 Mar 01 - 1895 Mar 04 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - 1895 Mar 05 - 1895 Mar 10 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - 1895 Mar 11 - 1895 Mar 13 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - 1895 Mar 14 - 1895 Mar 16 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - 1895 Mar 17 - 1895 Mar 21 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - 1895 Mar 22 - 1895 Mar 25 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - 1895 Mar 26 - 1895 Mar 31 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - 1895 Apr 01 - 1895 Apr 04 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - 1895 Apr 05 - 1895 Apr 08 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - 1895 Apr 09 - 1895 Apr 14 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - 1895 Apr 15 - 1895 Apr 18 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - 1895 Apr 19 - 1895 Apr 22 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - 1895 Apr 23 - 1895 Apr 26 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - 1895 Apr 27 - 1895 Apr 30 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - 1895 May 01 - 1895 May 06 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - 1895 May 07 - 1895 May 09 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - 1895 May 10 - 1895 May 13 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - 1895 May 14 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - 1895 May 15 - 1895 May 16 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - 1895 May 17 - 1895 May 19 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - 1895 May 20 - 1895 May 21 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - 1895 May 22 - 1895 May 24 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - 1895 May 25 - 1895 May 28 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - 1895 May 29 - 1895 May 31 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - 1895 Jun (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - 1895 Jul 01 - 1895 Jul 03 (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - 1895 Jul 04 - 1895 Jul 07 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - 1895 Jul 08 - 1895 Jul 11 (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - 1895 Jul 12 - 1895 Jul 14 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - 1895 Jul 15 - 1895 Jul 18 (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - 1895 Jul 19 - 1895 Jul 21 (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - 1895 Jul 22 - 1895 Jul 24 (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - 1895 Jul 25 - 1895 Jul 28 (Box 31, Folder 70)
  - 1895 Jul 29 - 1895 Jul 31 (Box 31, Folder 71)
  - 1895 Aug 01 - 1895 Aug 07 (Box 31, Folder 72)
  - 1895 Aug 08 - 1895 Aug 14 (Box 31, Folder 73)
  - 1895 Aug 15 - 1895 Aug 21 (Box 31, Folder 74)
  - 1895 Aug 22 - 1895 Aug 31 (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - 1895 Sep 01 - 1895 Sep 07 (Box 31, Folder 76)
  - 1895 Sep 08 - 1895 Sep 11 (Box 31, Folder 77)
  - 1895 Sep 12 - 1895 Sep 14 (Box 31, Folder 78)
  - 1895 Sep 15 - 1895 Sep 18 (Box 31, Folder 79)
  - 1895 Sep 19 - 1895 Sep 25 (Box 31, Folder 80)
  - 1895 Sep 26 - 1895 Sep 30 (Box 31, Folder 81)
  - 1895 Oct 01 - 1895 Oct 04 (Box 31, Folder 82)
  - 1895 Oct 05 - 1895 Oct 09 (Box 31, Folder 83)
  - 1895 Oct 10 - 1895 Oct 16 (Box 31, Folder 84)
  - 1895 Oct 17 - 1895 Oct 21 (Box 31, Folder 85)
  - 1895 Oct 22 - 1895 Oct 25 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 1895 Oct 26 - 1895 Oct 31 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 1895 Nov 01 - 1895 Nov 04 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 1895 Nov 05 - 1895 Nov 07 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 1895 Nov 08 - 1895 Nov 14 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 1895 Nov 15 - 1895 Nov 21 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 1895 Nov 22- 1895 Nov 28 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 1895 Nov 29 - 1895 Nov 30 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 1895 Dec 01 - 1895 Dec 07 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 1895 Dec 08 - 1895 Dec 14 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - 1895 Dec 15 - 1895 Dec 21 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - 1895 Dec 22 - 1895 Dec 26 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - 1895 Dec 27 - 1895 Dec 31 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - 1896 Jan 01 - 1896 Jan 05 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - 1896 Jan 06 - 1896 Jan 10 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - 1896 Jan 11 - 1896 Jan 16 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 1896 Jan 17 - 1896 Jan 21 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - 1896 Jan 22 - 1896 Jan 28 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - 1896 Jan 29 - 1896 Jan 31 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - 1896 Feb 01 - 1896 Feb 03 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - 1896 Feb 04 - 1896 Feb 06 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - 1896 Feb 07 - 1896 Feb 10 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - 1896 Feb 11 - 1896 Feb 14 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - 1896 Feb 15 - 1896 Feb 17 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - 1896 Feb 18 - 1896 Feb 21 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - 1896 Feb 22 - 1896 Feb 29 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - 1896 Mar 01 - 1896 Mar 04 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - 1896 Mar 05 - 1896 Mar 07 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - 1896 Mar 08 - 1896 Mar 11 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - 1896 Mar 12 - 1896 Mar 14 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - 1896 Mar 15 - 1896 Mar 21 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - 1896 Mar 22 - 1896 Mar 31 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - 1896 Apr 01 - 1896 Apr 07 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - 1896 Apr 08 - 1896 Apr 14 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - 1896 Apr 15 - 1896 Apr 21 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - 1896 Apr 22 - 1896 Apr 27 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - 1896 Apr 28 - 1896 Apr 30 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - 1896 May 01 - 1896 May 07 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - 1896 May 08 - 1896 May 14 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - 1896 May 15 - 1896 May 21 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - 1896 May 22 - 1896 May 26 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - 1896 May 27 - 1896 May 31 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - 1896 Jun 01 - 1896 Jun 04 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - 1896 Jun 05 - 1896 Jun 07 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - 1896 Jun 08 - 1896 Jun 09 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - 1896 Jun 10 - 1896 Jun 14 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - 1896 Jun 15 - 1896 Jun 21 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - 1896 Jun 22 - 1896 Jun 27 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - 1896 Jun 28 - 1896 Jun 30 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - 1896 Jul 01 - 1896 Jul 07 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - 1896 Jul 08 - 1896 Jul 14 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - 1896 Jul 15 - 1896 Jul 21 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - 1896 Jul 22 - 1896 Jul 26 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - 1896 Jul 27 - 1896 Jul 31 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - 1896 Aug 01 - 1896 Aug 04 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - 1896 Aug 05 - 1896 Aug 07 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - 1896 Aug 08 - 1896 Aug 12 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - 1896 Aug 13 - 1896 Aug 16 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - 1896 Aug 17 - 1896 Aug 19 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - 1896 Aug 20 - 1896 Aug 21 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - 1896 Aug 22 - 1896 Aug 27 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - 1896 Aug 28 - 1896 Aug 31 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - 1896 Sep 01 - 1896 Sep 09 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - 1896 Sep 10 - 1896 Sep 14 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - 1896 Sep 15 - 1896 Sep 21 (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - 1896 Sep 22 - 1896 Sep 30 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - 1896 Oct 01 - 1896 Oct 07 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - 1896 Oct 08 - 1896 Oct 14 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - 1896 Oct 15 - 1896 Oct 18 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - 1896 Oct 19 - 1896 Oct 22 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - 1896 Oct 23 - 1896 Oct 31 (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - 1896 Nov 01 - 1896 Nov 05 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - 1896 Nov 06 - 1896 Nov 08 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - 1896 Nov 09 - 1896 Nov 10 (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - 1896 Nov 11 - 1896 Nov 12 (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - 1896 Nov 13 - 1896 Nov 14 (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - 1896 Nov 15 - 1896 Nov 18 (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - 1896 Nov 19 - 1896 Nov 21 (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - 1896 Nov 22 - 1896 Nov 25 (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - 1896 Nov 26 - 1896 Nov 28 (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - 1896 Nov 29 - 1896 Nov 30 (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - 1896 Dec 01 - 1896 Dec 03 (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - 1896 Dec 04 - 1896 Dec 07 (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - 1896 Dec 08 - 1896 Dec 10 (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - 1896 Dec 11 - 1896 Dec 13 (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - 1896 Dec 14 - 1896 Dec 16 (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - 1896 Dec 17 - 1896 Dec 21 (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - 1896 Dec 22 - 1896 Dec 25 (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - 1896 Dec 26 - 1896 Dec 28 (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - 1896 Dec 29 - 1896 Dec 31 (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - 1897 Jan 01 - 1897 Jan 05 (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - 1897 Jan 06 - 1897 Jan 07 (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - 1897 Jan 08 - 1897 Jan 13 (Box 32, Folder 93)
  - 1897 Jan 14 - 1897 Jan 16 (Box 32, Folder 94)
  - 1897 Jan 18 - 1897 Jan 19 (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - 1897 Jan 20 - 1897 Jan 21 (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - 1897 Jan 22 - 1897 Jan 25 (Box 32, Folder 97)
  - 1897 Jan 26 - 1897 Jan 27 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 1897 Jan 28 - 1897 Jan 29 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 1897 Jan 30 - 1897 Jan 31 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 1897 Feb 01 - 1897 Feb 03 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 1897 Feb 04 - 1897 Feb 06 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1897 Feb 07 - 1897 Feb 08 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 1897 Feb 09 - 1897 Feb 11 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 1897 Feb 12 - 1897 Feb 14 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - 1897 Feb 15 - 1897 Feb 17 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 1897 Feb 18 - 1897 Feb 19 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - 1897 Feb 20 - 1897 Feb 23 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - 1897 Feb 24 - 1897 Feb 25 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - 1897 Feb 26 - 1897 Feb 28 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - 1897 Mar 01 - 1897 Mar 03 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - 1897 Mar 04 - 1897 Mar 07 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - 1897 Mar 08 - 1897 Mar 10 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - 1897 Mar 11 - 1897 Mar 12 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - 1897 Mar 13 - 1897 Mar 15 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - 1897 Mar 16 - 1897 Mar 17 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - 1897 Mar 18 - 1897 Mar 21 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - 1897 Mar 22 - 1897 Mar 23 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - 1897 Mar 24 - 1897 Mar 25 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - 1897 Mar 26 - 1897 Mar 28 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - 1897 Mar 29 - 1897 Mar 31 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - 1897 Apr 01 - 1897 Apr 02 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - 1897 Apr 03 - 1897 Apr 05 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - 1897 Apr 06 - 1897 Apr 07 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - 1897 Apr 08 - 1897 Apr 10 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - 1897 Apr 11 - 1897 Apr 14 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - 1897 Apr 15 - 1897 Apr 16 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - 1897 Apr 17 - 1897 Apr 18 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - 1897 Apr 19 - 1897 Apr 20 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - 1897 Apr 21 - 1897 Apr 23 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - 1897 Apr 24 - 1897 Apr 26 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - 1897 Apr 27 - 1897 Apr 28 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - 1897 Apr 29 - 1897 Apr 30 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - 1897 May 01 - 1897 May 04 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - 1897 May 05 - 1897 May 07 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - 1897 May 08 - 1897 May 11 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - 1897 May 12 - 1897 May 14 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - 1897 May 15 - 1897 May 18 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - 1897 May 19 - 1897 May 21 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - 1897 May 22 - 1897 May 24 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - 1897 May 25 - 1897 May 28 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - 1897 May 29 - 1897 May 31 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - 1897 Jun 01 - 1897 Jun 05 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - 1897 Jun 06 - 1897 Jun 09 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - 1897 Jun 10 - 1897 Jun 14 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - 1897 Jun 15 - 1897 Jun 17 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - 1897 Jun 18 - 1897 Jun 20 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - 1897 Jun 21 - 1897 Jun 24 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - 1897 Jun 25 - 1897 Jun 28 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - 1897 Jun 29 - 1897 Jun 30 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - 1897 Jul 01 - 1897 Jul 03 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - 1897 Jul 04 - 1897 Jul 07 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - 1897 Jul 08 - 1897 Jul 11 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - 1897 Jul 12 - 1897 Jul 14 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - 1897 Jul 15 - 1897 Jul 16 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - 1897 Jul 17 - 1897 Jul 20 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - 1897 Jul 21 - 1897 Jul 23 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - 1897 Jul 24 - 1897 Jul 27 (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - 1897 Jul 28 - 1897 Jul 31 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - 1897 Aug 01 - 1897 Aug 05 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - 1897 Aug 06 - 1897 Aug 07 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - 1897 Aug 08 - 1897 Aug 11 (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - 1897 Aug 12 - 1897 Aug 14 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - 1897 Aug 15 - 1897 Aug 18 (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - 1897 Aug 19 - 1897 Aug 21 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - 1897 Aug 22 - 1897 Aug 25 (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - 1897 Aug 26 - 1897 Aug 31 (Box 33, Folder 70)
  - 1897 Sep 01 - 1897 Sep 07 (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - 1897 Sep 08 - 1897 Sep 09 (Box 33, Folder 72)
  - 1897 Sep 10 - 1897 Sep 14 (Box 33, Folder 73)
  - 1897 Sep 15 - 1897 Sep 19 (Box 33, Folder 74)
  - 1897 Sep 20 - 1897 Sep 24 (Box 33, Folder 75)
  - 1897 Sep 27 - 1897 Sep 28 (Box 33, Folder 76)
  - 1897 Sep 29 - 1897 Sep 30 (Box 33, Folder 77)
  - 1897 Oct 01 - 1897 Oct 04 (Box 33, Folder 78)
  - 1897 Oct 05 - 1897 Oct 07 (Box 33, Folder 79)
  - 1897 Oct 08 - 1897 Oct 12 (Box 33, Folder 80)
  - 1897 Oct 13 - 1897 Oct 16 (Box 33, Folder 81)
  - 1897 Oct 17 - 1897 Oct 21 (Box 33, Folder 82)
  - 1897 Oct 22 - 1897 Oct 27 (Box 33, Folder 83)
  - 1897 Oct 28 - 1897 Oct 31 (Box 33, Folder 84)
  - 1897 Nov 01 - 1897 Nov 05 (Box 33, Folder 85)
  - 1897 Nov 06 - 1897 Nov 07 (Box 33, Folder 86)
  - 1897 Nov 08 - 1897 Nov 11 (Box 33, Folder 87)
  - 1897 Nov 12 - 1897 Nov 14 (Box 33, Folder 88)
  - 1897 Nov 15 - 1897 Nov 17 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - 1897 Nov 18 - 1897 Nov 21 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - 1897 Nov 22 - 1897 Nov 24 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 1897 Nov 26 - 1897 Nov 28 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 1897 Nov 29 - 1897 Nov 31 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 1897 Dec 01 - 1897 Dec 07 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 1897 Dec 08 - 1897 Dec 10 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - 1897 Dec 11 - 1897 Dec 14 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - 1897 Dec 15 - 1897 Dec 17 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 1897 Dec 18 - 1897 Dec 21 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - 1897 Dec 22 - 1897 Dec 24 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - 1897 Dec 25 - 1897 Dec 27 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - 1897 Dec 28 - 1897 Dec 31 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - 1898 Jan 01 - 1898 Jan 07 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - 1898 Jan 08 - 1898 Jan 11 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - 1898 Jan 12 - 1898 Jan 14 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - 1898 Jan 15 - 1898 Jan 21 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - 1898 Jan 22 - 1898 Jan 28 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - 1898 Jan 29 - 1898 Jan 31 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - 1898 Feb 01 - 1898 Feb 07 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - 1898 Feb 08 - 1898 Feb 10 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - 1898 Feb 11 - 1898 Feb 14 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - 1898 Feb 15 - 1898 Feb 17 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - 1898 Feb 18 - 1898 Feb 25 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - 1898 Feb 26 - 1898 Feb 28 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - 1898 Mar 01 - 1898 Mar 03 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - 1898 Mar 04 - 1898 Mar 07 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - 1898 Mar 08 - 1898 Mar 10 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - 1898 Mar 11 - 1898 Mar 14 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - 1898 Mar 15 - 1898 Mar 17 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - 1898 Mar 18 - 1898 Mar 21 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - 1898 Mar 22 - 1898 Mar 23 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - 1898 Mar 24 - 1898 Mar 28 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - 1898 Mar 29 - 1898 Mar 31 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - 1898 Apr 01 - 1898 Apr 04 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - 1898 Apr 05 - 1898 Apr 07 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - 1898 Apr 08 - 1898 Apr 11 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - 1898 Apr 12 - 1898 Apr 14 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - 1898 Apr 15 - 1898 Apr 17 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - 1898 Apr 18 - 1898 Apr 19 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - 1898 Apr 20 - 1898 Apr 21 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - 1898 Apr 22 - 1898 Apr 24 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - 1898 Apr 25 - 1898 Apr 26 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - 1898 Apr 27 - 1898 Apr 30 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - 1898 May 01 - 1898 May 04 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - 1898 May 05 - 1898 May 07 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - 1898 May 08 - 1898 May 11 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - 1898 May 12 - 1898 May 14 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - 1898 May 15 - 1898 May 18 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - 1898 May 19 - 1898 May 21 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - 1898 May 22 - 1898 May 26 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - 1898 May 27 - 1898 May 28 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - 1898 May 29 - 1898 May 31 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - 1898 Jun 01 - 1898 Jun 04 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - 1898 Jun 05 - 1898 Jun 07 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - 1898 Jun 08 - 1898 Jun 11 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - 1898 Jun 12 - 1898 Jun 14 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - 1898 Jun 15 - 1898 Jun 18 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - 1898 Jun 19 - 1898 Jun 21 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - 1898 Jun 22 - 1898 Jun 25 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - 1898 Jun 26 - 1898 Jun 30 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - 1898 Jul 01 - 1898 Jul 06 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - 1898 Jul 07 - 1898 Jul 12 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - 1898 Jul 13 - 1898 Jul 18 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - 1898 Jul 19 - 1898 Jul 25 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - 1898 Jul 26 - 1898 Jul 31 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - 1898 Aug 01 - 1898 Aug 07 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - 1898 Aug 08 - 1898 Aug 14 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - 1898 Aug 15 - 1898 Aug 21 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - 1898 Aug 22 - 1898 Aug 24 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - 1898 Aug 25 - 1898 Aug 28 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - 1898 Aug 29 - 1898 Aug 31 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - 1898 Sep 01 - 1898 Sep 04 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - 1898 Sep 05 - 1898 Sep 07 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - 1898 Sep 08 - 1898 Sep 10 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - 1898 Sep 11 - 1898 Sep 14 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - 1898 Sep 15 - 1898 Sep 19 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - 1898 Sep 20 - 1898 Sep 21 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - 1898 Sep 22 - 1898 Sep 28 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - 1898 Sep 29 - 1898 Sep 30 (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - 1898 Oct 01 - 1898 Oct 03 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - 1898 Oct 04 - 1898 Oct 07 (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - 1898 Oct 08 - 1898 Oct 11 (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - 1898 Oct 12 - 1898 Oct 14 (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - 1898 Oct 15 - 1898 Oct 20 (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - 1898 Oct 21 - 1898 Oct 25 (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - 1898 Oct 26 - 1898 Oct 31 (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - 1898 Nov 01 - 1898 Nov 05 (Box 34, Folder 88)
  - 1898 Nov 06 - 1898 Nov 07 (Box 34, Folder 89)
  - 1898 Nov 08 - 1898 Nov 10 (Box 34, Folder 90)
  - 1898 Nov 11 - 1898 Nov 14 (Box 34, Folder 91)
  - 1898 Nov 15 - 1898 Nov 21 (Box 34, Folder 92)
  - 1898 Nov 22 - 1898 Nov 26 (Box 34, Folder 93)
  - 1898 Nov 27 - 1898 Nov 30 (Box 34, Folder 94)
  - 1898 Dec 01 - 1898 Dec 02 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 1898 Dec 03 - 1898 Dec 07 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 1898 Dec 08 - 1898 Dec 14 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 1898 Dec 15 - 1898 Dec 21 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 1898 Dec 22 - 1898 Dec 31 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 1899 Jan 01 - 1899 Jan 07 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 1899 Jan 08 - 1899 Jan 19 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 1899 Jan 20 - 1899 Jan 24 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 1899 Jan 25 - 1899 Jan 26 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 1899 Jan 27 - 1899 Jan 29 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - 1899 Jan 30 - 1899 Jan 31 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - 1899 Feb 01 - 1899 Feb 02 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - 1899 Feb 03 - 1899 Feb 04 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - 1899 Feb 05 - 1899 Feb 06 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - 1899 Feb 07 - 1899 Feb 08 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - 1899 Feb 09 - 1899 Feb 10 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - 1899 Feb 11 - 1899 Feb 14 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - 1899 Feb 15 - 1899 Feb 16 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - 1899 Feb 17 - 1899 Feb 20 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - 1899 Feb 21 - 1899 Feb 24 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - 1899 Feb 25 - 1899 Feb 28 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - 1899 Mar 01 - 1899 Mar 03 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - 1899 Mar 04 - 1899 Mar 07 (Box 35, Folder 23)